tobook.com 2009-06-19

# toBook.com - Privacy policy

Privacy policy

Thank you for visiting the toBook Hotel Guide. Your privacy is very important to us. The following notice explains our online information practices and how your information is collected and used at this site. 

Our privacy policy is very simple:  
**We do not sell, rent or share your personal information with anyone.**

We will disclose individual personal information only if we are subpoenaed or ordered by a court of law. 

**Which personal information is collected**  
Like most websites, there is certain information we automatically track, including the URL that you just came from, which URL you next go to, the browser you are using, and your IP address. 

We use cookies to help users navigate efficiently between secure and non-secure pages of our site. By definition, a cookie is a block of text the site places in a file on your computer's hard drive. Although there are many uses for cookies, we utilize them to simply keep track of your preferences. Please note that a cookie cannot be run like a software program. It cannot be used as a virus to destroy files on your computer, cannot enable the Web server to read from your hard drive, nor can it create executable programs. Your browser can save cookie values to a file called cookies.txt if it needs to, but that is the limit of the effect on your system. 

If you register as a member of the website, personal information such as your name, address, phone number and email address are collected. You are also asked to create a login name and password to use on the site. Your personal information is stored for your convenience so you won't have to re-enter that information each time you make a reservation. 

**How is the information used**  
Personal information is not shared by anyone outside the toBook Hotel Guide organisation. 

We share aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and reservations with our suppliers and partners, but these statistics do not include any personally identifying information. 

When you make a reservation on our site, your personal and credit card information are forwarded to the property in which you have reserved. The property will use this information to process your reservation. A representative of that property or one of our Customer Support representatives may contact you if there is a question about your reservation. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or would like more information about our company, please contact us.
